LAUGHING MAN FANSUBS
Angels and demons were circling over me,
Crossing a brambly path of stars and milky ways.
He who does not perceive his calling,
does not know true happiness.
Watch in awe! Watch in awe!
Flying in glory, Flying in glory
I am calling, calling now. Spirits rise and falling.
To be with you longer
Calling, calling...
in the depth of longing
To stay myself longer
The flow may swallow you, flying in glory
A
Modest
Rebellion
This...
Is this the factory that still produces androids?
It's smaller than I thought.
Androids committing mass suicide...
It's something the media would want to know about.
I'll give you ten minutes.
While I am questioning the person in charge,
You go and check inside the production line.
Roger that.
Tachikoma, do you understand?
Of course! I'm a pro you know.
Get the factory owner.
Take that to the warehouse.
I am Aramaki from Public Safety Section 9.
I came here to question you about the
androids you created that committed suicide.
I'm Abe, the factory owner.
I'm sorry to have caused such trouble.
It seems that all of them were of the same type.
Yes.
Type GA07-JL.
It's the type that was known as "Jerry" to users.
It sold well when it first came out,
but only 8.000 or so are still active nationwide.
Frankly, it's not our top seller anymore.
We only manufacture parts
for maintenance purposes now.
Ishikawa.
I'm listening, I'll look it up.
The design is old now and its
movement and speech are awkward,
so we're not sure how much longer
we'll continue making the parts.
Do you have any idea why the
machine type Jerry was targeted?
Well, I think I do...
Jerry was the type that a lot
of users modified improperly.
Our superiors were actually happy and said
to let it be if that makes the thing sell.
The young workers from our
factory are creeped out because
they think the Jerrys cursed
their fate and committed suicide.
Warning: Virus detected!
Please help us find out what happened.
Do not worry.
Major, let's go.
Excuse me.
There's no doubt that it was caused by a virus.
Someone snuck it into the
periodic examination program...
and infected every user's Jerry
that connected via the internet.
One of the Jerrys that was sent back
to the factory for a repair examination
contained a time-based virus that
infected the factory's program.
I'm having Ishikawa analyse
the inside just in case.
So it's a public user's crime.
Do you think it's unrelated
to the case at the Capitol?
Most likely.
But we still need to confirm it, right?
I got a hold of the list of Jerry users.
Start with those who have a higher priority.
Send the list to Batou and Pazu.
I already did.
We'll head for the first house.
Tachikoma, return to Section
9 and wait for orders.
Sorry, but its seems there's
no role for you in this.
Hey Major...
According to what I've heard I get
a present if I stay home, right?
In that case, after I get back I'll tell you all the
exciting details of what happened until you get sick of it.
Exciting details?
Yeah! Yeah!
So it's starting to ask for presents now, eh?
Ishikawa?
Yes.
I'm done analysing the virus.
It's a virus that was made by an amateur, it's very
different from the virus that was found in the Capitol.
Yes.
One thing that worried me is
that I found a protection code.
Warning: Virus detected!
This program is protected.
So it was made to protect the creator's machine.
That means there's a high probability
that the culprit has a normal Jerry.
Most likely.
What about the factory owner's story?
It seems he was telling the truth.
They stopped manufacturing the
type 07-JL three years ago.
But I have confirmed multiple complaints from
hardcore users who opposed stopping production.
Send that info to the others.
You did well for the short amount of time given.
What's the matter?
I got complimented.
Did the police find out?
I changed locations multiple times, though.
I can't live without you.
Yes you can.
But I don't want to.
Will you be with me?
Yes.
Let's go to Italy together.
What are we going to do there?
We'll think about it after we go.
Sadness is meaningless.
I would choose nothing instead of sadness.
A weird case of androids simultaneously
committing suicide has been reported.
Today we have Mr. Miyashiro,
a modern sociologist, here as our guest.
First of all Mr Miyashiro,
what do you think about this case?
Androids are not life forms,
so it's not "suicide".
We should call it "self-destruction".
There're rumours that the robots are starting
to gain Ghosts like in certain old SF comics.
That's hard to believe.
It could be that this crime is done for
the pleasure of making people believe that.
This is stupid.
Really, I see...
Concentrate on the investigation.
Jerry was fairly popular in those days.
Its performance wasn't
spectacular, but it was cute.
I haven't seen any lately.
If you don't see them around, it
means our investigation will be easier.
And because of this case,
the already small number of
machines will become even smaller.
But why are we handling this kind of case?
We should have let the police handle it.
Did you forget about that robot-related incident
that happened last month at the Capitol?
That robot was also made by Genesis Andross.
I remember that, but this case and
that case are almost unrelated, right?
We have to investigate a link that
will most likely be non-existent...
So, you want to say, "this isn't our job"?
This is what they mean by "Preparing
for the one in 10.000 chance."
It means the other 9999 instances will be nothing.
We still don't know where the virus originated.
We've already begun.
Let's start investigating
from the top of the list.
Let's get this job done quickly.
Being a public officers is just great.
You're rough as usual.
I can open it without breaking
it if you let me do it.
You take too much time.
This guy must be a movie freak.
Warning. Virus detected!
Did you find something?
It's the virus that was planted in the Jerrys.
We hit the right spot.
Major...
We found the target.
He's pretty cunning, we were a little late.
I will send you our current
location and the info we collected.
Now we have to wait for Ishikawa's info.
Come on, spill it.
We don't record where the sex doll androids go.
Stop it. This place isn't it.
Again?
How boring.
I have confirmed the culprit's identity.
He's the son of the Canadian
ambassador, Marshal McLachlan. Age 26.
Height, 179 cm.
He has never been arrested.
He returned to his homeland once eight years ago,
but he came back here to Japan
to avoid military service.
An ambassador's son? Maybe we can't touch him.
I will negotiate with his home
country to revoke his immunity.
What is the culprit's current location?
He is heading towards the
Fukuoka area using Loop number 6.
That rich kid is driving such a nice car.
From the IR system's picture,
it seems a Jerry is riding with him.
That's a Jerry for sure.
Guide him off the highway when
you think the time is right.
Then corner him in a blind alley.
We will take clear action from there.
Got it?
Roger.
How nice, his last drive is
going to be along the coast.
His idea of buying a robot and customizing
it into an ideal girlfriend is so "macho".
I hate it.
"Macho"? And why are you saying this, Major?
That sure is an opinion that
values the female perspective.
He probably makes her stay at
home to do laundry and cooking.
But I don't think it can cook something fancy.
I don't think it was possible to achieve
that functionality at that price back then.
Then what does he make her do?
Don't get mad at me.
Maybe he places her somewhere,
and gazes at her all day.
So he is "macho".
Like I said before, why are you saying this Major?
Why would he be attached to an
old piece of junk robot anyway?
There are always guys who
can't get over the nostalgia
of old devices that can't
be bought with money.
He might get along well with you.
Cut it out!
You still use this old car, too.
In my case, it's purely love of the machine.
What are you doing?
Looking.
Why are you looking?
Because I am looking.
Your face looks best from the side.
It is very like you.
Aren't there a lot of people who
are more beautiful than me though?
But it's weird.
I don't get along with them well
and it makes me feel miserable.
Are you afraid?
I'm afraid, but I got used to it.
Can you say something nice to me?
I don't know that either.
Do you believe in the existence of souls?
I only believe in kindness.
Damn it. It's under construction.
I won't let it end the same way again.
Looks like he got off the
highway just as we planned.
Please head him off now Major, Sir.
Leave it to me.
So she overrode the GPS and
created a fake traffic jam.
Isn't it fun to work under a competent captain?
Yep.
Guidance complete.
We have to thank the Major.
Now we have to wait for the old monkey man.
There they are.
Batou.
We succeeded in getting his immunity revoked.
Go.
Roger.
He's an ambassador's son.
Let's try not to hurt him.
Of course.
I'll try to finish it off by just talking.
I was better at negotiating
than at fighting and using guns.
I bet.
I can't watch.
He can't run away quickly with a Jerry.
I'm Marshall McLachlan,
son of the Canadian ambassador Harvard McLachlan.
You can't arrest me!
Your immunity was revoked by
your home country a while ago.
What...?
Why?
Damn it, so it's not possible then...
Stay back!
Wait.
We just want to be together.
Don't interfere with us!
Let's go, Jerry.
Jerry, what are you doing?
Did you go insane?
No, I'm sane.
Wait, no, I did go insane.
I don't want to go with you.
I don't want to love you anymore.
Who called that a piece of junk?
She talks more than the ones at Section 9.
I'm sorry.
I really loved you.
What's happened?
That sure was an incomprehensible case.
Really?
I thought it was a case that
was very easy to understand.
In the end, it was proven that it had
nothing to do with the case at the Capitol.
How do you perceive this case?
A threat against the manufacturer by a
young mecha-maniac who felt nostalgic for old robots.
But it's ironic that this case was the clincher
to cease production of the spare parts.
Maybe he wanted to make his
android the only woman to exist.
So you're saying that he destroyed the
rest of the Jerrys because of that?
His motive was simple although
the method he used was clumsy.
Hey, hey, hey.
That's unusual, you're being sentimental.
Even if that was the case,
he put a protection code on his Jerry.
So why did his Jerry become insane in the end?
No other viruses were found on it.
Are you saying that the Jerry helped the man?
Jerrys are robots with no Ghosts.
When I was little,
I remember crushing an important doll
and crying because I couldn't
use my cyborg body well.
But you're one of the world's
best cyborg body users now.
Welcome home.
Are you watching old movies again?
20th century videos are the best.
Did you go insane?
No, I'm sane.
Wait, no, I did go insane.
I don't want to love you anymore.
What are you doing? It was about to end.
Did you go insane?
No, I'm sane.
Wait, no, I did go insane.
I don't want to love you anymore.
So this was the origin.
Sadness is meaningless.
I would choose nothing instead of sadness.
Do you believe in the existence of souls?
I only believe in kindness.
Did you go insane?
No, I'm sane.
Wait, no, I did go insane.
I don't want to love you anymore.
The words that the Jerry said last aren't here.
Hey, there is another line after this, right?
No, there isn’t. It's a perfect un-cut version.
She's so cold and human
It's something humans do
She stays so cold in her soul, she's so number 9
She's incredible math
Just incredible math
And is she really human?
She says there's something new
But when you live in flower just a mountain bloom
I smell lithium now
Smelling lithium now
How... is she what she doesn't say
She doesn't say
How is she when she doesn't suffer
I wonder what she does when she wakes up
When she wakes up